Imagine these two cowboys inheriting the one place in the west everyone
wants to get their hands on .... "The Cheyenne Social Club."
The Cheyenne Social Club is a western, comedy film directed by Gene Kelly.
Two cowboys inherit a "social club" specializing in satisfying men.
John O'Hanlan, played by James Stewart.
Harley Sullivan, played by Henry Fonda.
Jenny, played by Shirley Jones.
Opal Ann, played by Sue Ane Langdon.
Pauline, played by Elaine Devry.
Barkeeper - Great Plains Saloon, played by Robert Middleton.
The Cheyenne Social Club is a 1970 American Western comedy film written by James Lee Barrett, directed
and produced by Gene Kelly, and starring James Stewart, Henry Fonda and Shirley Jones.
The film is about an aging cowboy who inherits a brothel and decides to turn it into a respectable
boarding house, against the wishes of both the townspeople and the ladies working there.
The tone is lighthearted.